MATTHEW FRIES

(925) 787-1903 m@matthewfries.org matthewfries.org

7756 29th ave NW Seattle, WA 98117

2011 Knox Ave Apt. 403 Bellingham, WA 98225

PROFILE

Hello! My name is Matthew, and I am currently a student at Whatcom Community College, as well as a server at Fremont Bowl in Seattle. I have experience working in high intensity food service settings, doing everything from cooking pizza to taking orders and answering phones, and experience working in a fast paced retail environment. I graduated from Ballard High School in 2021, and am passionate about the outdoors, conservation, climbing, hiking, skiing, backpacking, coffee, and more. I am a quick learner, who can adapt to any situation very easily. I have many skills outside of food service and customer service as well, including photography, programming, and Adobe and Microsoft office software.

EXPERIENCE

Server, Fremont Bowl; Seattle, WA — June 2022-Present Responsible for:

- · Taking orders
- · Answering phones
- preparing orders for pickup
- · Customer service
- · General restaurant stocking and other related roles

General merchandise, Target; Seattle, WA — May 2022- June 2022 Responsible for:

- Guest Services
- Stocking
- · Food and Beverage related tasks
- Electronics
- Making sure product is off the truck and where it needs to be in a timely manner

General Employee, Veraci Pizza; Seattle, WA — November 2019-April 2020, March 2021-May 2021

Responsible for:

- Taking orders
- · Answering Phones
- Preparing food
- · Cooking food
- Washing dishes
- POS system

General Employee, Sunny Hill; Seattle, WA — April 2020-June 2020 Responsible for:

- Preparing food
- · Washing dishes
- Answering phones

EDUCATION

Whatcom Community College, 2022- present Ballard High School class of 2021

SKILLS

- · Customer service
- · General Retail
- Food prep
- Phone calls
- Quick learning ability
- Highly motivated
- Knowledge of web design, including HTML and Bootstrap Studio
- Adobe software, including Photoshop, Lightroom, and Illustrator
- Microsoft Office/google suite/apple suite
- Very tech savvy